Hey, how's it going everyone?
My name is John, and some of you, uh, may have never met me,
but, uh, if it's our first time meeting, nice to meet you.
I am the founder of Econ
and I just want to thank you for being a part of the, uh,
UGC Content Creation team, uh,
and, uh, working with us on this upcoming project.
We're super excited about it.
Uh, so this video's purpose is basically to get you aligned,
to get you introduced to the project, um, that you guys, uh,
basically signed up for.
So, uh, this document, uh, is, is not in,
it's not gonna have like exact
scripting or anything like that.
I wanna leave that guys up, leave that up to you.
But, um, because I'll be responsible for a lot
of the creative direction for the project, uh, I just want
to make sure you guys are aligned and know what to expect.
And if you have any questions, you can reach out to, um,
to Naja or me.
But my goal is to,
after you guys review this, we can get on a,
on a Zoom call together where we can all kind
of have questions or get aligned on the project.
And, um, and yeah, so let's just get straight into it.
So obviously, if you've never worked with us
before, we're called econs.
We do a lot of, um, content creation ourselves in-House,
and this is one of the first projects we're actually doing
outsource, uh, UGC content creation.
Uh, I, I know, uh, for some of you, we've, we've worked
with you in the past, but, um,
what's different about this one is we are relying on you
to do, uh, the full production aspect of things, uh,
from scripting all the way to editing.
Um, but we'll get into those details a little bit later.
But the brand that we are working with is called Thera Ice,
and we've actually worked with them, we've been working
with them for years, uh, a few years now.
We've done a lot of content for them,
and they really want to, uh, expand their content.
So they hired us to, um, to do that.
So you guys can check out their website here.
You can also check out their Amazon listing here.
This is where, uh, I would say a lot of people find them.
Um, they've done very well for themselves in terms
of the company growth.
Uh, I, I believe they have an amazing product.
It really works. And, um, one thing that I will mention is
that they just came, they just were hit
with some serious FDA compliance, um,
let's say setbacks.
Uh, that is basically like the product is meant
to, they have two products.
They have a, a therapy co, uh, headache relief cap,
and they have, uh, a cold
and hot therapy sleeve for like, post recovery
and stuff and, and things like that.
But they positioned the product as a headache relief cap
for, for years now, ever since they first got started.
But because the FDA came in, they basically said
that they cannot say that it helps prevent headaches, um,
because that's just, you know, they got to a point where
they kind of like, yeah, they're, they're just after them.
So they had to reword everything
that the company had in terms of the copy.
Um, and so if you open up this document, you can see exactly
what we're allowed to say and what we're not allowed to say.
So I definitely recommend going
through this on your own time
and looking at the words to avoid.
So we can't say Rx, we can't see headache.
This is like the main one, right?
We can't say compression or migraine pain.
Pain relief reduces inflammation.
Any ailments, uh, doesn't cure heal.
Uh, so for now,
staying away from from saying head is hurting
and my head hurts, these are all like, common things
that you would normally say, oh my God, it works so well
for my headaches, da, da, da.
Um, we want to replace those words with, uh, oh my gosh,
it's such soothing relief,
or this relief from my head is the relief
from my head is just incredible.
Um, it, it really helps relieve discomfort.
You know, we can say discomfort.
Uh, I can just feel my stress melting away.
Um, you know, this is the best cold therapy I've had.
Uh, and, and the list goes on and on, right?
So we don't want to get any, like, we,
we just wanna avoid that as much as possible.
We actually just went through
and like gutted a lot of their previous videos with us
to exclude any of those words.
So it's a bummer.
But, um, to side on, you know, to avoid any revisions
or anything like that, let's just make sure we're
avoiding any of those words.
So have a look at that document when,
uh, when you guys get the chance.
So, uh, if you've never seen this product, basically, um,
it's something you put over your head just like this.
Uh, you put it into the freezer
and you also put it into the microwave
for cold and hot therapy.
It's, it, it's amazing. It works super well.
It's one of the, you know, I actually have one at home.
I use it in the morning. I use it if I'm stressed out.
Um, but it's almost like it has
so many different benefits to it.
And, um, you know, in terms of headaches as well as, uh,
you can't say that, but, but headaches, stress relief, um,
to wind down, you know, de-stress meditate, there's
so many uses for it, and we'll go over that in a second.
So that's the product, the first product.
And some of you are only shooting this, this cap, so, um,
the other one won't apply to you.
Uh, the other one is a sleeve,
which has the same functionality,
but it's meant for your elbows, your knees, post-workout,
um, you know, during workouts you can use it, you know,
to relax and to recover basically.
So that one's pretty self-explanatory.
Um, over here under best performing ads,
this is actually some of the ads that we've done
for them in the past that have done very, very well.
Um, we, you don't have to necessarily like shoot it
or edit it like this, you know, we had shot this in-house
and then edited it on.
Yeah. But, uh, you can kind of see like,
in terms of the reaction
and the authenticity that we're trying to,
to create with you guys.
Um, that's what we're going after.
But you can see like, you know, he's talking to camera
and he is wearing the products, like, this works very well.
So if we said this, if we did a similar,
similar style without, you know, saying any of those, uh,
those blocked words, then we're gonna be in good shape.
So you can have a look and go through some of these ads,
but basically they're all UGC for the most part.
You know, we've done a little bit of like combining clips
together, but, um, yeah, you, you can have a look at that.
So the scope of the project is we're gonna be, uh,
requesting five individual U GCs from you.
So each one of these videos will be its own standalone
video, um, which will require you to do the scripting,
the shooting, as well as the editing.
However way you do that on your own, um, you know,
feel free, we do recommend you shoot with, uh,
with a phone versus any like, gear
or like any like, nice camera.
I don't think that's necessary.
Um, we do ask that you require the raw footage.
Uh, feel free to delete any takes, you know,
you don't think were usable,
but we, we do ask that you'll, you provide the raw footage,
shoot everything vertically, um, nine by 16 like this,
and keep the length of the videos under 60 seconds.
That would be great. Um,
and if you can include three different hooks to the videos,
um, these could be, you know, lines or visuals
and what, we can go into that in a second.
But, um, that's super helpful for us, especially.
'cause we're gonna be testing all, all your content
and seeing which ones perform best,
and if they perform well for us, then we'll be reaching out
to do, uh, a second month with you
and can hopefully continue the process.
Uh, and so that's really the benefit of doing this.
If you guys do a great job.
Um, we wanna work with you, um, for the next one
and the next one, just
because it's so much, you know,
you've already learned the product and you know how it works
and da, da da.
So, um, what we ask of you in terms
of assets is the final video without any titles.
Um, and then the final video with titles.
So if you're, you know, using Cap Cut
or if you're using Premier, like,
just give us a version without any titles on it, subtitles,
um, and then give us one
with like the finishing touches on it, that would be ideal.
And then, uh, B roll shots.
So I have a breakdown of the B roll shots down below.
So when coming up with the angles for your own videos, um,
here are a couple that you know from their research
and data, like things that we want to test, uh, and,
and new things that could potentially relate to you.
So number one,
and these aren't in specific order of like importance,
it's just the number of angles that we, we had come up with,
but de-stressing, uh, whatever that means to you.
Getting I immediate stress relief after a gnarly day.
That's what I put down for me, you know, as a parent, uh, I,
I love, you know, after a long day working
and watching my kids, this de-stresses me.
Um, I can just chill on the,
chill on the bed and, and use it.
Beauty salons. Um, you know, this is kind of like,
I would say not really my area,
but if you know, for any of the females out there,
if this is something you can relate to,
feel free to talk about it.
Um, at home Spa, get relaxing at Home Spa Treatment.
I think this one's pretty self-explanatory,
but, um, if you, you know, like, it's like,
it's like getting some sort of, you know, you can get,
it feels like an at-home spa, you know,
by getting that cold therapy.
Uh, so play on that angle.
Number four is cold therapy,
helping shock your body like a cold bath.
This is something that I, I like to do in the morning where,
you know, to wake me up, I'll put it on my head immediately.
It's like splashing yourself with, with cold water just
to kind of get the, the blood going.
Um, so that's, that's a possible angle.
Meditation, you can wear it while you meditate.
Sports recovery, um, whether, you know,
you're doing the sleeve or the hat, either one, like
after a long workout, this is definitely something, uh, to,
to wear, uh, for hot or cold, uh, therapy.
Number seven, that's spelled wrong. Angel seven.
But, uh, coffee Alternative.
Okay, so this is for people who, I mean,
I'm a big coffee drinker,
but you know, this could be something as like, you drink,
you, you wear it in the morning, like I said, where it kind
of replaces that cup of coffee.
Um, so you can show yourself, you know,
throwing a coffee cup away
or yeah, whatever you can, you can,
you can wear it as a boost of energy,
like it definitely does wake you up.
Skin icing, using this as a substitute
to ice cubes on your face.
I think getting like a shot of that would be awesome.
I know I have puffy eyes, so it kind of,
it helps get rid of those puffy eyes.
Um, so if you wanna put an ice cube on your eyes as like a,
like a scroll stopper
or a hook, that would be, that'd be sweet.
Um, self-care nighttime routine
where this reduce puff puffiness and relax before bed.
So there's a ton of different angles here that sh
that whatever applies to you that feels really natural
to you and authentic to you.
Please go ahead, keep those in mind and,
and embed those into the videos.
So there's a five, uh, five total videos that I would love
to get from you guys.
And number one is a reaction video. Okay?
This is like, probably the most valuable one
because it's like super authentic.
You know, when you guys put this thing on
for the first time, I'm telling you,
if you haven't already like it, it's gonna blow your mind.
It's like super soft, whatever.
I'm not gonna explain, I'm not gonna ruin it for you,
but really want you guys to capture this moment.
Um, you know, set your phone up on a tripod,
set it down somewhere, um,
and then just kind of walk through the process
and talk about it as you feel it, you know, explain it.
That's really what sells.
And I think that's what gets people really excited about it.
Um, but as you're doing that, make sure not to mention any
of the noncompliant terms.
I know it's so easy to be like when you're in the moment,
oh, this feels so good for my headaches.
But, you know, try to keep
that in mind when you're actually doing the video.
This next, uh, the next one is, uh, unboxing how
to plus voiceover.
This, this process is, you know, your standard video, okay,
I just got my Thera Ice in the mail.
I'm gonna put it in the freezer. Um, you know, I,
I'm gonna wear it to relax for the day,
or I just had a long day at work, so I'm super excited
to unbox my Thera Ice.
Um, you know, things like that. It's pretty standard.
I, I, I think these days on, on social,
but I would love to, oh yeah, make sure not
to show the packaging,
because the packaging has some uncompliant terms.
They haven't up updated the packaging yet,
so please make sure to not show that on camera.
You can maybe flip it upside down, um, or
however way, uh, to avoid it.
Number three is a testimonial.
So this is just like talking straight to camera,
holding the product in hand
and like some good natural lighting,
talking about your own personal benefits
or like what you love about it.
Um, you know, you can use any of these angles up top
and mention them as you, as you do the testimonial.
Uh, feel free to talk about whatever, you know,
whatever comes to mind for you.
Next is a demonstration video.
So demonstrate this video in different
settings and use cases.
Use it while meditating, getting rid of, uh, eye bags, cold
and hot therapy de-stressing after a long day.
So this is something that, you know,
we just really wanna see this thing in
action as much as possible.
So I'll leave it to you guys to, to kind of narrate that.
Uh, and number five is lifestyle aesthetic.
This is all about shooting it in natural lighting,
making it look pretty nice and calming.
Um, I imagine kind of like lofi
lofi beats in the background, um, you know, reading a book,
uh, meditating, working, you know, things like that.
We, we don't, we don't want this one to be like,
super fast paced and like in your face.
It's just more, all right, I like this.
I like this to chill. All right, next,
we have some b b-roll shots
that we'd love to get from you guys.
Uh, obviously reactions, uh, reacting to the texture as well
as the, the cold, the cold therapy aspect to it.
Unboxing, uh, like I said
before, don't show the, uh, the container
or the actual packaging itself
because it's, um, it's uncompliant, uh,
putting it into the freezer, putting it into the microwave.
These are all self-explanatory,
wearing it in different places.
So the couch bed, watching tv, your desk, anywhere else
that you, you like to chill out in your house,
wearing it while meditating could be anywhere.
Um, and then hooks and pain points.
So if we can get you, you know, drinking coffee
and throwing it away, or like holding a Starbucks cup
and you know, we're, we're, we can do like side
by side shots later on, um,
wearing an ice pack on your head, like, you know,
it's something you don't want to be doing, uh,
or showing how inconvenient the ice pack is,
rubbing it on rubbing your head and pain
and stress kinda like this.
Like, ugh, gosh.
Um, and then lastly,
putting ice cubes on your eye bags, like right here.
I think there'd be some cool shots there,
but, um, we'll use these, uh, you know, it,
we'll edit these ourselves into, into your videos.
But, um, ultimately, like I would say
this is the outline of videos, um, to get more clarity,
I would love to just get on a call with everybody just
so we can spitball some more ideas
and get clearer so we know what we're doing.
But that is the creative brief.
Hope you guys, um, are excited.
I'm super excited, uh,
especially if it's our first time working together
and I'm looking forward to, um,
what we're able to create together.
Alright, I'm gonna wrap it up there.
Thanks so much for watching, guys. Bye.